I think Caribbean people, we don't realize our privilege.
We are very dismissive of the Black American experience.
Oh, you all just have a chip on your shoulder.
You all need to just keep your head down and just work.
And it's like, yo, we grew up having Black teachers, Black politicians, Black leaders, Black doctors, Black dentists.
Not to say we don't have colorism, classism, and versions of racism in the Caribbean.
But we are very privileged that we can walk in anywhere and we're the majority, 99.99999% of the time.
So we have a certain sense of security that no matter what, home is home.
But for me, coming to the U.S., when I go to New Orleans, I love that.
I've been there like 15 times.
I will be there and New Orleans is like 70% Black and I feel like I love there.
But in some places, I'll be there and I'll just see the American flag.
I'll be like, yo, it just feels heavier, like it don't fit there.